- Be careful, be careful.
- Wow~
Is this this heavy?
- Hey, hey, hey, hey...
- Oh my.
Park Byun?
ha
taste of victory
pro bono
Ah, why is your expression like this?
yes?
Ah, we won.
more neatly than this
Can you win?
Did I tell you?
‘There is no such thing as defeat in David Kang’s dictionary’
Ah, yes
Ah, but why is that?
Like a person who has seen something he couldn't see
No
I was just, ah, nervous.
I feel a bit sick...
Oh my, Park Byun
It's still far away
This is my pride
I am a current minister
While being detained by the court
one eyebrow
I'm a person who doesn't give a shit, I
just a person
The incident where I just cut him with a knife was also me.
After that, I had some sour intestine soup.
He said he was a wonton person.
Speaking of lawyers...
Judge Kang!
Oh my, Inspector!
Haha
Hey, it’s been a while since I’ve had this!
Captain!
kid…
Roger!
Oh, how have you been?
How are your knees? How are your knees?
child, crucible
Now it's really cool
Thanks to the judge
I'm not a judge anymore
child
You're away for a moment.
You need to come back soon.
Thank you, Inspector.
Please come back soon!
Captain!
Roger!
Go
Yes, take care of yourself.
Oh yeah, haha
- Awesome!
- oh my
That's good
You are very popular.
Huh!
Let’s see how good it is.
Hahahahaha
Lawyer Kang
yes
Attorney Kang is a good person, right?
Suddenly out of nowhere?
- No.
- Ah...
What's not
I really hate this kind of thing
What are you trying to say but not doing it?
What is it? tell me
I just want to be a good person
Lawyer Kang
Joy!
- Sister!
- Hehe~
Sister, it’s been a while.
Oh! What's going on
You say you're crazy busy?
Oh my, I
High Court Sexual Violence Task Force
Are you as busy as the judge?
They say criminals pray?
‘Only Judge Jeong Eui-hyeon, the Grim Reaper.
Please let me avoid it'
So who is going to sin?
Come on, let’s eat something delicious.
Let's go, let's go
Umm
Are you divided on likes and dislikes?
What is a national judge from a dirt spoon?
You were famous
Among young judges
There were some people who didn't like it
Honestly I don't like it
Sister? why?
Do you care too much about popularity?
I do too many media interviews.
But
That kind of person
Why did you suddenly stop trading?
As a candidate for Supreme Court Justice
I heard your name was going up and down?
fact
There was a strange rumor
What is it?
In the court president's secretary's office
It's a story that just came out.
There was suspicion of bribery...
her! what?
Well, how about a box of apples?
There is a sinister rumor
I guess the higher-ups are hissing
Because of the court's honor
Jeong, is it really true?
I respect you, really.
Lawyer Kang
Wow…
Even until I lost in the first trial
I was really at a loss
Now
Have you all memorized it now?
We are unconditional!
I win
Definitely win!
I lacked faith
How would you like me to massage your shoulders?
no, it's okay
yes
But
Chairman Choi Woong-san
Kang Hoon adopted his mother
Attorney Kang too
Isn’t this something you didn’t expect at all?
Huh
I didn't expect it.
It's all me
Looking ahead from the beginning...
I got caught, I got caught
I can't believe I got caught.
I strategically…
Getting caught
Your skills are amazing.
Of course, getting caught is actually...
No, I got caught.
You mean no?
hello
- Are you here?
- Hey, are you here?
Park Byeon
yes
Ah, now
Because Attorney Park also came.
Hosted by a coalition of human rights groups in the Gyeonggi region
There is an early soccer tournament.
We are also a public defense team
Everyone is required to attend.
Uniforms came out too.
- Yes!
- Okay.
Well, these days
I heard the Yangchon-gun team is doing well.
No~
Well, I don’t know what a law firm lawyer is, huh?
Ah, on the weekends, I spend time with clients.
Playing golf gracefully
Shouldn’t it be business?
'elegance'…
I also like kicking balls.
In the past
- I kicked the ball a bit too.
- Huh?
But
On this golden weekend, yes?
It's over 30 degrees outside now.
Early soccer?
not my style
I can't go
They
Because you're our client.
Local human rights groups, farmer groups!
I don't!
ruler! Everyone knew, right? uh?
As soon as you start, go all out for 5 minutes!
It's a pressure attack, yes?
When I'm not watching the referee
You can be rough, rough, huh?
If anyone steals the ball
Right to me
I'm in front, right in front
To me, to me, to me
You're giving me a pass, okay?
Let's get messy, get messy
child
Don't act like a saenim, just
- Get dirty, okay?
- Attorney Kang
I'll say it again
How far can this place go?
Something that strengthens friendship and solidarity...
In the game
Where is the goodwill!
Win or lose!
yes…
New Pro Bono Team Leader
You are full of fighting spirit.
Yes, in victory
He's a bit obsessive...
Oh, an obsessed man?
and!
what?
Where did you recruit him from?
ruler! Guys, you can't lose
Gather together! Gather together!
ruler!
Two, three!
Co-byeon, co-byeon Avengers!
The Avengers!
mutual greetings
Oh my, Attorney Kang.
A taste of German style soccer today
Please take a look and go
Ha, what is German...
It must be Yangchon-ri style~
What is it?
Would you like me to read your palm?
Here's a preview, today's score
oh big bread
bread
I…
Now, now, now, block, block!
Block it!
Hey, catch it, catch it!
Hold it there! Cross…
Ugh!
- No, no foul.
- Foul!
Foul!
Long bye, long bye!
- and!
- what are you doing!
Ha, really…
See you again!
Okay, 1 to 1!
Jang Byeon! Jang, Jang, Hwang Jun-woo!
and!
Oh, are you doing that on purpose?
I push it here like this.
I have to stop it here
What if I fall here?
Block, block, block, block
Wow!
- It's our goalpost.
-What are you doing...
- No, outside...
- Are you crazy, are you crazy?
- What, are you confused?
- what…
Baby, out...
Ha, I will change the strategy.
When Harvard catches the ball
I'll focus and mark everything.
Everyone gather together, everyone, everyone, everyone.
If you steal the ball!
Pass, shoot, goal, shoot, goal
Pass, goal, goal, goal, goal
and
Hwang Jun-woo is out
Jang Yeong-sil out
Yoo Nan-hee Go!
Park Gippeum
Go!
Uh, don't come!
Oh, what should I do!
Oh my my my, why are you like that!
Why, why, what's going on?
No, I hit it very gently.
No, I only pushed a little bit.
Yoo Nan-hee Nice!
No, someone is hurt now!
- Ugh!
- no…
Uh, uh, uh!
Don't come, don't come, don't come
- Don't come! uh?
- Ah, evil!
Ah, ah, ah, evil!
no!
Ugh, uh!
- That's a miracle.
- Huh?
You got it right
oh big bread
joy!
You said you would teach me how to win?
hmm…
Wait a minute!
It's not over yet
Huh?
We are lawyers
Even if I lose the score
I didn't lose the match
Wow!
- Wow, wow!
- Chief!
Boy, really…
- Ah, sir...
- kid!
Wow...
yes? A cheating player?
Even in early soccer.
There is a rule.
No matter how much you want to win
To local soccer
Do you recruit foreign mercenaries?
No, wait a minute.
Lawyer Kang
Why?
A mercenary?
Oh, well, oh...
Oh, well, then, then that, well
Is this person Korean?
I'm Korean, right?
My dad is Nigerian
My mom is Korean
I was born in Korea too
Oh my...
kid…
Hey, then, what?
What, this, this
Is this person Korean?
My mom is from Iran
My dad is Korean
kid, yeah
He, dad, he
You met my mom on a trip to Tehran.
My mom is Egyptian
Yeah, that
Cairo trade
Working together with mom and dad
It happened like this, and
Mom is so pretty
No, the people of Seoul
Do you think you live in a different world?
What?
Ah, yes, Attorney Kang.
Oh, we are in Yangchon-gun
What is the percentage of multicultural families?
Don’t you know about multicultural families?
Ha, I lost the game too
- Have good manners
- Let's go, sister.
Wow, I'm embarrassed
Yeah, whatever
Okay, whatever.
This problem
Let's do it on the next date.
yes, yes
Go, go, go, go, let's go together!
- Goodbye.
- long stool, long stool
Let’s go together!
- ah…
- Oh my...
direction! direction! Jojo!
Is it really necessary to do this?
It's so trivial
Kid!
from a local human rights group.
This is a requested case.
I really need you to ask me a favor
To human rights
Where are the little things?
Yes, it's a divorce case.
You can get an estimate just by looking at it.
I want to come to Korea and make money
International marriage through broker
After receiving a marriage visa
File for divorce right after you finish adjusting?
There are a lot of things like this these days.
Let's try something like this
There's no benefit
Hello, let's go this way.
To whom
Are you saying there is nothing to gain?
yes?
Oh, of course
To our pro bono team
That means there is no benefit.
Lawyer Kang’s popularity
I guess that doesn't help.
You have done many things that deserve applause.
The voice of a national lawyer
You should listen
Ha~ it's me, Park Byeon
Another day
Do you see me as such a shallow person?
no
I see you as someone with a thick face.
Park Byun, these days
Why are you being so mean to me?
Did I do something wrong?
Do you have any?
yes?
Oh, don't do that.
Please meet me sometime.
I played soccer a few days ago
They say you’re coming from Yangchon-gun.
That yangchon at that time?
yes
Come here from that village.
Well, go to a local human rights group.
from a local human rights group.
It's a requested case.
I just said...
Welcome!
uh?
Then…
Bleak beak?
It's really cool, it's really cool
Is this the pro bono team?
- No?
- kid…
That's right
What's going on?
i want to divorce
please help
The client
It's this person
Umm
Oh~
Lawyer
It’s completely different from on the soccer field, isn’t it?
What happens on the soccer field...
don't do it
I don't like that dance very much
Oh, but Kaya.
You speak Korean very well, right?
How long have you been here?
Me for 2 years?
2, 2 years…
But how...
I studied since I was young
Korean
'Time with you'
'Everyone was dazzling'
‘Because it’s a nice day’
'Because the weather is not good'
'Because the day is suitable'
'Every day was good'
‘Goblin’ was so good
I guess you liked Korean dramas.
Korea in the drama was my dream.
everything is pretty
- It was so shiny.
- Ugh
I like pretty things a lot
Me too
And…
You must be disappointed.
Korea in reality
When you open the goblin door and go out
appearing
Because it's not a fairytale place
So I'm not saying I'm going to divorce.
I'm a childish child
Well, it’s not like that.
Then what is the reason?
Uh…
Personality difference
personality differences
Is that all?
korean people
That's all divorce.
Am I not good enough for that?
Kaya, that's not it.
How to file for divorce
difficult to continue marriage
There must be a serious reason
Is there a specific reason?
uh…
Me and my husband
I keep doubting
What kind of suspicion?
There's another guy
Are there any?
Lawyer Kang
I need to check the facts
Are there any?
I saw you that day
Do you think you'll be popular?
why?
Am I pretty?
Do my thoughts matter?
Kaya, the thoughts of those around you are important.
That's for other people
Please ask
Anyway
I don't have it
another man
But my husband said without any basis
Do you have doubts?
'A bitch to kill'
I swear like this
Take away my cell phone
I keep doubting
i want to divorce
Like other Korean women
Are you saying I shouldn't take the job?
why?
You also brought the counseling records.
Abuse due to serious suspicion
This is grounds for divorce.
Is this a public interest case?
Then no?
Who is this public interest for?
what does that mean
Ha, designer clothes and sunglasses
I saw you show up wearing a scarf.
I heard you come from a poor hill tribe family.
Korea Dream
I think I achieved it right
That's right
The reason for divorce does not change.
Those clothes from earlier
It's a luxury product, but it's a copy.
Yes?
It also seemed handmade.
Just by looking at it
Cheap fabric sold at the market
Come to think of it
The last cheerleader clothes
The skirt looks like it was sewn.
- Oh, really?
- Yes
But how does Jang-byeon know that?
It's no big deal, just before
Working on sewing union activities in Cheonggyecheon
I just learned a little bit
Oh, really?
But how does Jang-byeon know that?
That's not it!
Boy, what the hell is Jang Byeon-eun?
What kind of life have you been living?
I have so much doubt
I'm worried about that.
Mr. Kaya
It seems like you have a very lively personality.
Kid! Okay, yes, yes
Well, let's say it's true.
It's not a divorce by agreement.
Do you really want to divorce in court?
What could be the reason?
Hey, you know Park Byun too.
A person who came to Korea on a marriage visa
If you just divorce by agreement
I can't live in Korea anymore.
Divorce due to reasons attributable to the other party
Get a marriage breakup visa
Wouldn’t it be possible to stay in Korea?
Ah~
I see.
Oh, then it's easy
A fresh start is possible, huh?
Ah, either way…
in my hometown
I brought my boyfriend
You can get married again
Of course there are people like that.
But before even taking over the case,
Should we start with preconceived notions?
Attorney Hwang
- Oh, no, yeah.
- Yes
But we, well
I can't do everything in the world
This thing called priority
- This…
- It is also a public interest.
In the end, isn’t it for the benefit of Korean society?
no, tough guy
There are a lot of Korean people!
Oh, why...
Mr. Kaya
I married a Korean person
I am living in Korea
- Wow...
- Ms. Kaya
Are you not a member of Korean society?
- ah…
- Any member of society
To receive protection from the law
Making it
I think that's public interest
What do you think?
- Mmm
- No, well, Korea.
To be protected by the law,
From the time of Grandfather Dangun
Do you even need a genealogy?
ah…
Or, whatever.
Well, a box full of apples
Should I at least bring it?
huh?
Park Byun, what did you say just now?
That's right!
Now, now
Everyone, don’t do this.
First, conduct an on-site investigation.
Make your decision
If Yangchon-gun
There will be a lot of edible mushrooms too.
Wood ear mushrooms, net mushrooms, cauliflower mushrooms
If you do well, Cordyceps sinensis
- Wow
- Oh!
That would be nice
Ah
Everyone, please investigate the site... yes
When I say ‘Cordyceps sinensis’
I will 'fight', yes
Why Cordyceps sinensis?
- Cordyceps sinensis
- Fighting!
why are you doing this
Cordyceps sinensis?
- Just do it!
- Let's try it.
There's a lot of gossip
When Cordyceps sinensis appears
It's really awesome
Brother, stop it, please
That, Park Byun
A little bit about me these days
It seems like you're being cold towards me?
Oh my
When was I hot?
ha
What, about me, what
Have you heard anything strange?
why?
Is there something holding you back?
Kenggi…
It’s so cool
I am
One point looking up at the sky
I am a person without shame, I
Okay, then
What…
Well, what is ‘okay, then’?
It's done
Well, whatever happened…
Didn't it work out for me?
Hold on tight
Ouch! Mr.
Oh great lawyer!
Oh great bam!
Oh no
Oh my, that, this
A busy lawyer
Take a break on the weekend
What are you doing up to here?
Ah, aren’t we a public defense?
It often comes down like this
I also help out
The precious meaning of a drop of sweat, well
Should I say that I am reflecting on it?
Oh no, not a drop of sweat
kid, that
Is it because I powdered it a lot?
Boy, it looks like an egg ghost
Haha
The sun is a little strong today
But it's okay
I grew up in the country too, yeah
Well, this much sunlight, well.
No, because of this sunlight
The peppers are growing very fresh...
Oh my
Oh my, oh my, oh my!
oh my! Oh my, lawyer.
Oh my, are you okay? uh?
Oh my~
Oh my, that
He has an egg-like face
Oh my
Oh great lawyer!
Wow...
Is it really okay if I don’t go to the hospital?
Wow, what
What kind of hospital would you go to for something like this?
Wow, I have to go back to work...
Oh my, oh my, oh my, oh my!
Oh my, oh my
- That's it.
- Oh my, my...
That's enough, that's enough
Take a break, ‘Take a Break’
Is that so?
Oh, but those gentlemen who came with me
How come you’re so good at your job?
Who?
- huh?
- be careful
-Thank you!
- Departure
please give me more
Tskcha
- Let's go!
-I'll go~
- Let's go
-What kind of woman is strong?
- Oh
- Oh, thank you!
Here we go!
Ouch!
Hey, are you okay?
eww!
- eww!
- her! uh…
Ugh
Hey, hey, hey, hey
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey
Ouch!
- uh!
- Oh my...
it's awesome!
Oh my
Look at those long legs
How is it that Hou Dae is so fine?
Bachelor!
If you fix all that
Please take a look at the eaves of my house too.
Sure, sister
I will definitely help you
Oh my, I must be crazy
It's your sister!
Uh~you
Mr. Lawyer
The message is very guilty, guilty, huh?
I know?
Why are you not good at it?
Then, I go back to work...
- Oh my, my!
That's it, that's it
'Take a Break'
- Huh?
- Oh my.
Enjoy your meal, Chief!
Uh, uh, yeah
New, new, uh
Come on! Well, everyone, newbies, take it!
Hey guys, come!
Oh my, lawyers.
Haha, this is like Yangchon-ri
It's really diverse, right?
Yes, now
This is Tang Mien.
Chinese noodles, ‘Zhongguomien’
Ah, this is called pancit bihon.
- Philippine Japchae
- Oh~
Ah, the old man is that, that
Thai food somtam
In terms of Korea,
Well, it's like kimchi.
And that in front
Uh, Gogeo is Vietnamese Buncha.
Ugh, eat whatever you like.
- I will eat well.
- Yes, yes, yes, yes.
Wow~
It's almost like a hotel buffet, right?
Oh my, everything, this
Our daughters-in-law prepared it, well.
It's 'We Are the World', huh?
‘We Are the World’
Hey, this
Is the stew right?
Oh, and the Korean daughter-in-law too
Do you think there is one?
Oh, that zucchini stew
Kaya did it
The governor's daughter-in-law
i did it
It's delicious, right?
yes
Now, now, that
Would you like to have a glass of makgeolli?
Okay, cheers everyone!
Cheers!
‘Cheers’, ‘Kanpai’, ‘Busuku’
‘Ssukrungri’, ‘Sseolrang’
Oh, Chief, what the hell?
How many languages do you speak?
language
It's genius
Genius…
um
- Stop eating, boss.
- Wow
Now, let's take a look at the information we've all gathered.
Let's talk
Ha, but the story is
This is all strangely mixed...
Oh my~
Don't even talk
Kaya, since she came here
The village men
Are you saying it was all a lie?
Even so, it’s like a woman
Wear strange clothes day and night
I don't know where all the money comes from~
But the kid was nice, right?
huh?
Oh, my parents-in-law like the centipede.
That, zucchini stew
I asked how to boil it.
I wrote it down in my notebook.
Oh, the governor’s son?
Thanks to my parents, I got such a wife.
What a world...
I said this, but
The governor's daughter-in-law
The kid...
a little…
There's a rumor that he's gay
Really?
no, just
The sound of people whispering
That's right
Someone else's words without any basis
If you do it carelessly, you will be punished.
no, just
If anyone asks, just
Because I laugh carelessly
The village men were saying hellelere~...
My sister Kaya
nice
You dress me up day and night
Wow
Take a pretty picture
Wow, you are really pretty.
Hey, hold on to that senile old lady.
What are you talking about?
Hello, I…
Kaya, about her relationship with men.
There are a lot of rumors
There seemed to be no basis
So
Oh, honestly
It was a bit uncomfortable to listen to.
No, Kaya is from a bar.
I guess there was even a rumor.
Ah, how could you say something like that so carelessly...
- under…
- What about Park Byeondo?
Is there such a thing as fantasy in the countryside?
yes?
Friendly, humane and helpful to each other
All of that
It's a fantasy that only appears in dramas.
Lots of jealousy
Talking a lot about other people in the world
Usually it's pretty wide
If something really hard happens
He said he didn't know me
That's the real countryside.
Oh, what are they doing here?
Oh, hurry guys
Well, change your clothes and come out.
Oh, that, the governor
That in Seoul
Great people came
They said they would take me to their house.
Whoa, house, huh, whoa!
yes, welcome
yes, nice to meet you
Oh, thank you for inviting me to dinner.
thank you so much
in Seoul
These busy lawyers
He came to our neighborhood to help with work.
how can i
Are you saying you don’t know me?
Honey, there are guests here.
Welcome
Oh my, what should I do?
Isn’t your house so shabby?
- Oh oil~
- No, no, no.
No, this much
You don’t have to worry about it.
The house is so pretty
Thank you, hahaha
Oh, I'm not ready for dinner
For now, please come to the separate building.
- Yes
- Now, come here.
come this way
This is a separate building
- Wow
- Haha, baby!
Ah, yes!
Guests came here
- Oh, hello!
- Yeah.
Uh, Kaya.
I guess it's a work space?
Oh, yes, that's the room where clothes are made.
Huh, wow
The room is so pretty
This kid
very talented
at my house
I just got lucky.
Our pretty sexy girl
Good Kaya…
- Sexy!
- Uh, honey.
Ugh!
Are you done?
- ah…
- Now play with me.
- Ah...
- Dongminah
Bird, bird, sexy!
Just play with me
Ah, honey
You have guests here.
Let's go quickly
Dongmin, that’s not true!
Mr. Kaya!
- I missed you.
- No
That, that, that guy, that…
You'll only play with me!
No, I'm not really that kind of guy...
I haven't prepared anything
Eat a lot
Were you very surprised a while ago?
This is my son
The child is sexy
It's because I like it so much
my child
It's because I hurt my head when I was young.
He's a really nice and gentle kid.
Me, but
Kaya, don’t we eat together?
My child is a little shy.
Couple
I eat well in comfort.
Are you still newlyweds?
Then in the evening
Are you only staying in a separate building?
- Going out...
- Nanhee.
No, yes
Now, this
This is a very precious ginseng wine that I received as a gift.
Come on, let's have a drink.
Because I'm driving...
Ah, yes
Governor, do you really like orchids?
Do you like orchids?
Boy, I'm an outsider, but
The person who sent it
If you are Lee Hak-ju
Ungcheon
District court chief?
yes
That's right, really
They say it's okay
Why bother sending something like that?
Ah, our county governor
Even though they say it’s done, it’s done
people don't listen
Now, let’s eat.
Ah, yes
- I will eat well.
- Yes~
Enjoy your meal!
“Joie de viva”
What do you think?
no
It's just that I came back from the countryside.
It reminds me of the old days...
You said that earlier, right?
Usually it's pretty wide
If something really hard happens
They say I don’t know
Maybe in your hometown
What happened?
hmm…
Well, it's no big deal.
What is the law?
That they are not on the side of the common people
Are you sure you learned that one thing?
If it's the law
Could it be…
In our situation
What kind of lawsuit are you filing?
Where do you get the money for a lawyer?
I'll do it
Because I will do everything
I hope mom gets better quickly
Oh, you still
They say it’s because they don’t know much about the world.
Ha…
Who can help a house like ours?
There's no one, David.
If you have no money and no power,
You're lonely, you know?
Could you help me now?
yes?
Like Attorney Kang back then.
People who are lonely because they have no money or power
Maybe you can help now?
So that you don't get lonely
I'm sorry
Without even knowing what’s going on
Speaking carelessly
Ha, this is me.
Get some rest
It's okay
Bird, bird, sexy!
Just play with me
Dongmin, that’s not true!
Mr. Kaya!
You'll only play with me!
At the partner meeting
Are you telling me not to do Kaya’s case?
Let’s find out about another incident…
yes? why?
There is insufficient evidence to support
It doesn’t really help the firm’s image…
Let's do it
- This incident
- Yes?
Wow, suddenly?
no
Foreign daughter-in-law divorce case
What public interest case is this?
It's a private interest case.
Lawyer
difficult to receive legal protection
on immigrant women's human rights
It's an incident
If we don't help
It's hard to get help otherwise...
immigrants, refugees
You should try something like this
It's hard to hear good things
Oh, he, Attorney Park
Understand the mood of the world these days
Is this not working?
It's hard to make a living
Even though people say I'm going to die, I'm going to die
Immigrant women’s human rights?
Hey, who told me to come to Korea?
Did he threaten you with a knife?
It's a hit, a hit!
- what?
- It's going to be a hit.
Hit?
To the governor's house who has been rich in land for generations
intellectually disabled husband
A smart person who lives in captivity
Attractive foreign daughter-in-law
It's a story that the media will be excited about.
It will be a hot topic
Lawyer Kang
A public defense team that doesn't make money
The reason you put it
Isn't this publicity?
Malicious comments are better than no comments.
This is an event worth betting on.
Okay, that's it.
Since the arrival of our national judge
It's very breathtaking
Ah, like this
A person who likes to receive attention
Why did you come to our firm?
I don't know why I make noise every time.
Child…
Oh my, I'm sorry.
It's late
Everyone was bored without me, right?
Wow, oh lawyer
You must be busy, and you have meetings like this...
Now, what is the conclusion?
Is it already grown?
Oh, of course
So is the social atmosphere these days.
An incident like this...
That's right
This is the social atmosphere these days.
Of course it should be done, this kind of incident
Oh my, oh the lawyer
What do you mean by that?
Hey, who are these days?
Do you want to work in a factory or farm?
clients doing business
Because I couldn't find someone
There was a lot of chaos, very
To attract cheap and good labor
Even if you come to Korea
Something that says you won't have to suffer anything unfair
Signal?
Should I send it?
Please take care of me
Attorney Kang, Attorney Park
I'm going down first.
thank you
For helping me
You helped me?
I?
Isn't it?
Attorney Gippeum Park
He was a fun person?
Attorney Park? why?
You were threatening me?
I have a video from you
What?
Oh my, hey, hey, hey, hey
Why are you showing me this?
Oh, lawyer too
You already knew that, right?
Why is Attorney Kang
Did he suddenly quit being a judge?
Why do you think so?
two minutes
I heard you were a fellow student at the training center.
Well then you know
Lawyer Kang has no money or power.
Life as a public interest lawyer
It's a character you can't choose.
Even so,
Our Pro Bono Team
not a laundromat
Appointing a person with weaknesses as team leader
A place that does image washing
I mean no
Hmm…
Without raising the issue publicly
The reason I came here directly like this is
something
Does that mean you have something to ask for?
I just
So that we can work hard
Oh the lawyer
I hope you support me
Please support me?
Led by Attorney Kang
Pro Bono Team
With my own achievements
You're promoting it extensively.
That level of responsibility
Shouldn’t you lose?
Attorney Kang is our team leader.
Qualified or not?
Until it becomes clear
Oh my, Park Byun really…
Park Byun really said that?
again
I need to get him on the M&A team.
Do you have a talent for negotiation?
Fish oil! It's just my style
No, ah…
Hey, Park Byun, that video...
Where on earth is that video...
Take care of it
Huh?
So that Park Byun doesn’t act erratically.
IC
Lawyer Kang
From an immigrant human rights organization
You said you were commissioned, right?
Is there something like a shelter there?
Worth a temporary shelter?
-There is
- During divorce proceedings
Kaya, let’s do a favor there.
It won't take long
Yes?
Well, there is still evidence to win the case.
Nothing came out, right?
Mr. Kaya
It itself is evidence
What does that mean?
Among the stories I heard from residents:
Was there anything strange?
huh?
Kaya's outfit
Clothes, attire?
swimming! uh?
no, just a kid
The clothes are just too short, huh?
Dressing carelessly
Why is that?
think about it
Kaya's outfit seen this time
Well, what
I'm afraid I'll get sunburned while working on the farm...
Then
What was the day you came to our office?
It was very hot that day
35 degrees
Huh?
Well, just two weeks ago
in 2 weeks
The fact that my clothes changed drastically
Something happened.
In the scorching 35 degree heat
With my neck wrapped tightly
need to be covered
work
I brought my sister
thank you
Ah…
You can't keep coming to the neighborhood.
People look at me strangely
It only takes a moment
That day when I played soccer
I danced in Kaya’s outfit.
There was a rumor in the village, right?
Even so, I always like Kaya.
The villagers who looked at me with disapproval
They probably exaggerated it and made a fuss.
Is your husband very angry?
lock hanging on window
Does your husband have a sweet tooth?
You'll only play with me!
Mr. Kaya
Anyway, I mustered up courage
You've decided to divorce.
You have to be honest
WE CAN HELP
The scarf around the neck
What are you covering?
This, this is just…
Who do you want to protect?
husband?
If you file a criminal complaint
It will give you an advantage in your divorce trial.
That's not possible!
Mr. Kaya
If you want
I'll just let you divorce quietly.
really
Can you really just divorce?
yes
Ha…
Plaintiff's representative?
Reasons for filing for divorce
What happens?
yes
Suspicion, verbal abuse, and
Mr. Kaya
It's an attempted murder
Mr. Alyona
You are from Kazakhstan, right?
yes
At a restaurant in town
You are working
yes
You know Kaya here, right?
yes we
In the Korean language study room
We are studying together
On the evening of the last 2 days
Kaya's husband
Have you seen it in a restaurant?
- Yes
- About what I saw that day
Could you please tell me?
- Let's have a drink.
- Yes
Have a drink
- Is it delicious?
- Yes
Ah, you bastard.
When it's time to eat this
Be a good guard to your slut, you bastard.
Our sexy?
Fish oil~
Yeah, nigga, you slut
How was it when Gya played soccer last time?
Do you know?
why?
Our sexy girl is nice
To be nice, Mr.
Hey, I can see your pants
Just wearing short clothes
Did you see it? That
limbs, just, mr.
I was all embarrassed to see it.
Be careful~
Guys who are after your sexiness
Aren't there just one or two?
This time too, after soccer
I heard we all went to karaoke together?
What time did you come in?
Did you come in?
Because we are friends
I'm talking for you
Outside, Mr.
There are only thieves and bastards.
Don't lie!
Aren’t we sexy?
under…
- Okay, hey!
- Hey, hey, man.
Hey, man, hey, got it!
Oh, what a surprise, Mr.
Plaintiff's own newspaper
Let's get started
That evening
I can't hear well
please speak louder
Yes, sorry, that…
in the evening
After finishing farming
I went home
Honey!
Honey, what are you doing!
That's the clothes I made
- Evil!
- Clothes like this
Don't wear clothes like this!
- Oh, honey, don't do this!
- Hand, cell phone!
Give me your phone!
why?
- Cell phone, cell phone!
- ah…
- Argh!
- no way!
-Give me the phone!
- evil!
Just stay with me now!
Don't go out in the evening!
Just stay with me!
You don't go out in the evening!
I study Korean every evening!
You're Korean!
You don’t need to speak Korean!
Just stay with me!
honey!
iced coffee!
And then
I came back very drunk late at night.
A drunk husband
Holding the plaintiff's shoulders
I shook it wildly
You mean he strangled me?
yes
Don't lie!
Please sit down
Ha…
So you even fainted?
yes
That's it, your honor.
Your honor
Now the plaintiff has no basis
They are framing the defendant.
To the defendant
Taking advantage of having a disability
You're making things up that don't exist.
The wound remaining on the plaintiff's neck
Can't you see it yet?
To strangle a person like that
This is attempted murder!
Oh no!
yes?
My husband is a good person.
Uh, I did that by mistake.
That thing that tells me to die
Absolutely not
i know
It's a real mistake
Judge, my husband.
don't go to jail
Yes?
Don't make a show!
That gross thing
Well, this place
It's divorce court.
It's not a criminal court.
- Well, whether it was intentional or not.
- Ha…
'Because of the defendant's doubts, the plaintiff
'Marriage life
'To the extent that it is difficult to sustain'
'I feel very dangerous'
This is our argument
Your honor
The defense will also request witnesses.
There are many witnesses.
Please allocate enough time
Okay
The due date is set for 2 o'clock in 3 weeks.
Oh my, it was hard, right?
thank you
It's still too early to be thankful
Because it's just the beginning
Well, Jang Byeon went to see the chief, right?
Did you testify?
As expected
That, Kaya’s in-laws.
It has been a big name in the neighborhood for several generations.
No one will want to come forward easily.
Ah…
work because of me
It seems like it keeps getting bigger
It's a bit difficult
Since it was a small town, rumors must have spread.
Mr. Kaya
I just think about Kaya.
Don't think about others
Okay?
thank you
See you next time in court.
yes
Lawyer Kang
Did you call the reporters?
If you're going to do it without anyone knowing, why do it?
A case where you don’t get any money?
I hope we can just divorce quietly.
Mr. Kaya
You know how much I wish for it
Don't look at me like that.
Someone who is as good at trading as me
Yes?
I heard that you visited CEO Oh Jeong-in.
Why don't you ask me anything?
- What?
- You know.
You don't even want to know?
- Attorney Kang
- Yes
We're on trial right now.
Talk to you later.
Attorney Kang’s problem is
'That's your problem' That's it
I thought we were one team...
defendant
Let's start your own newspaper.
yes, i understand
late that night
When you come home drunk
Have you ever strangled your wife?
no
please speak louder
No, no
No, no, I wasn't sleepy.
Then
holding on to my wife's shoulder
Have you ever shaken it?
Please answer me, defendant.
yes
'Hold on to my shoulders
'I've been shaken before'
Why did you do that?
Please tell me
I'm going
speaking
‘Go’?
Where did your wife say you were going?
Yes, to my parents’ home, to my parents’ home.
My parents?
Did you say you were going back to your home country?
- Yes
- Let me summarize.
'That night
'I came home drunk'
'The wife suddenly
'He said he would return to his country'
'So I was surprised'
‘There were times when I grabbed my shoulder and shook it’
'I never strangled him'
Is that correct?
yes
that bitch
That ungrateful girl
It's all set up
our good son
Accused of attempted murder?
That damn bitch!
Witness, this is the court.
Please be careful of your words and actions
Ha…
Sorry, Judge.
I feel so unfair
The black-headed beast
They say it's not something to collect
Ah…
Now, witness.
The witness is the plaintiff
'On purpose, as a friend
'I said I was going back'
‘I provoked the defendant’
Is this how you see it?
I have an objection
This is a Judo newspaper
I admit it
Okay, let me change my question.
Why did the witness
I did this in a planned way
He filed for divorce in court.
Do you think?
Do you have any basis?
yes, there is
Please tell me
That kid
In this house in the first place
I didn't plan on staying long.
It's a house with precious hands.
I was anxious about why I couldn’t have a child.
There was a reason for it all
I heard this from a pharmacist in my neighborhood.
witness
In Yangchon-eup
You run a pharmacy, right?
yes
There's a manuscript
Did you see it at the pharmacy recently?
yes
What kind of medicine were you looking for?
that is…
Pharmacist
Huh? Welcome
What are you looking for?
that…
Do you have that?
Medicine that won't make babies
Huh?
Birth control pills?
No, why is that?
Oh my, it's a boat
My stomach hurts so bad, oh
Give me some medicine, I think I have an upset stomach.
- Wait a minute, from here…
- ah…
It was very strange
A precious thing from the governor's hand
The whole neighborhood knows this
No, your daughter-in-law
Why are you looking for birth control pills?
fact
You shouldn't do this
Without even realizing it, I told the governor’s wife
‘What’s going on?’
‘Is there some problem with my son and his wife?’
I ended up asking, stop.
Your honor
Regarding the testimony just now
The defendant's mother
defendant couple's room
Found deep in the closet
I will submit evidence.
It's a contraceptive pill
Ha…
Your honor
The manuscript is like this
I will build a happy family with the defendant.
I had no thoughts
How much the defendant wants the child
Even though I clearly knew it
Suddenly I want to go to my parents' house
Provoke the defendant by speaking
The defendant was surprised
Hold the plaintiff's arm tightly
Leave bruises behind
This is all for divorce
It was just preparation work.
can't see
The defendant
Because my nature is kind
Let's not do anything more
Even strangulation marks later.
By manipulating it
It was put on the defendant.
No~
How can you do this with your own hands?
Can you strangle yourself?
Evidence that the defendant did this
It's a dash!
Yes, for real!
Your honor
postponed
There is one new thing
What is that?
Oh, actually, the defendant's mother that day
I probably didn't know because I was traveling with friends.
Actually that night
The defendant
With a fainted plaintiff
I went to the town hospital
To be precise
to the animal hospital
-Why...
- what…
The party who witnessed the defendant
May I apply as a witness?
here and now
Are there any witnesses?
yes
Attorney Jang!
Ah
Uh, chief?
Because I don’t know anything!
I thought you were here to help with work
To ruin the village
They are all noblemen.
Ah! Damn it, Mr.
Ah!
Ugh
I understand
In this neighborhood, the governor's house
It won't be easy to live without
Mr. Kaya
I am a foreigner from far away...
Right?
When the chief's mother was young,
I heard you worked as a nurse in Germany?
huh?
How...
My father was a miner stationed in Germany.
The two of you met in a far away country
So you're a married couple, huh...
Until the director was ten years old
I heard you lived in Germany?
how
Did you play some soccer back then?
Among the big German kids?
It was very difficult, right?
lonely and
This time
The manager can help you
leave home
Everyone who settled in Yangchon
So that you don't get lonely
So as not to be sad
that night
That friend
Self-indulgence
brought to our hospital
It was past 12 o'clock at night.
The door was slammed so hard...
What was the condition of the manuscript at the time?
I passed out from exhaustion.
It was limp
What should I do?
There were bruises on my arms
I had something like a towel wrapped around my neck.
When I took it off,
There was a red handprint.
Fortunately, I was able to massage my hands and feet.
I gave him some water
I came to my senses
‘What is this?’
‘Should I call the police?’
Well, I was worried.
Well, not another house.
The governor's house...
It's work
Well, the condition is not serious.
kid, i'm sorry
Why didn't you tell me?
Because I'm scared
Uh, actually
that night
I have a photo taken
Because the wound on my neck was severe
I took a picture just in case.
Oh, will I get caught up in something useless?
Did you erase it because you were scared?
But
There is still a file
It was left in the trash can
- Yes
- Ah...
yes, yes
What should I do?
It's terrible, really.
Witness, that…
It must have been late at night at the time.
what to ride
Did the witness come to the hospital?
That guy can't drive
Because it’s the countryside
Well, there are no taxis either.
Oh, he came running
You came running?
How far is that?
Well, well…
From the governor’s house to our hospital
Will it be 3km?
3km
that distance
So you ran carrying Kaya on your back?
Yes, I risk my life
It looked like he ran over?
My whole body is covered in sweat
Ugh
Your honor
Please proceed with the anniversary.
I have some things to review
Why…
Why are you doing this?
Oh, why are you doing that?
No, the director even took a picture.
You submitted everything.
Anyone can see that the trial is over.
Why suddenly again...
Everything happens in the world
It's not what it seems
Yes?
Why did you lie?
Lawyer Kang
strangulation
Isn't that your husband?
yes?
What are you talking about?
To my parents
I said I would go back
My husband was surprised
I grabbed Kaya's arm and shook it.
So it's true that I fainted
I was strangled
before my husband came in
It must have happened
So I'm already in shock
I was so exhausted
Isn't it?
Keep in mind
There were things that caught me off guard.
‘Indeed, the people of Yangchon-ri’
'Let's all kiss together
'Are you lying?'
If not…
Oh, the governor’s son?
That friend is a bit lacking, though.
Very nice
Even if someone criticizes me, I say ‘heh~’
Well, even if you hit me, ‘heh’
You just laugh?
The village people all
About Kaya's husband
We are talking about the same thing
‘He is a person who cannot kill even a bug.’
Kaya herself
As a matter of fact, my husband
They say he's a good person
Well, just now
Carrying Kaya on my back
He risked his life by running 3km at night.
I'm listening to the story
Something kept bothering me
'That kind of person'
‘A person who is that kind’
'Finger marks
'To the point where it flies clearly'
‘Can you strangle a person?’
No
Ha, Park Byeon
Look at the picture again
This photo was taken right after the incident.
The scars are more obvious
What do you think of the bruises?
On the right side of Kaya's neck
There is a long handprint
But does this look like a thumb?
So I guess you pressed it with your right hand?
You must be right handed!
Mr. Kaya
Is your husband right-handed?
That's not true
I saw it in court
Really, Kaya?
What happened to this?
The opposing lawyer
I'm not stupid
Everything will be revealed in the end
Why, why...
Why are you lying like this? yes?
under…
There's one more strange thing
At the pharmacy
The day I went to get birth control pills
That day, of course
It was the day after this incident.
And my mother-in-law found it
Submitted contraceptive pills
That
That's the morning after pill.
This is the drug
Morning after pill…
Ah, no way…
You need to talk.
On that day...
what happened that day
Did it happen, yes?
My mother-in-law and her friends
Go on a trip and leave home
My husband was drinking
The day I didn't come home until late at night
What's going on, Kaya!
uh…
under…
Now I understand
Why is Kaya like this?
Was there a lot to hide from the beginning?
Even though I decided to divorce
Why did you end up worrying about your husband?
Lawyer Kang
What are you talking about?
What happened?
Among the information collected by Hwang Byun,
Did you have any trouble?
Uh, if that’s what Hwang Jun-woo heard…
Ah, a centipede
My in-laws like it
That, zucchini stew
I asked how to boil it.
I wrote it down in my notebook.
Oh my
What do you mean?
These days, my father-in-law
Because I don’t like preparing food for you
When it's meal time
I heard you went out to drink on purpose?
Fish oil! It was bad, it was bad.
Uh…
father-in-law
Alone with my father-in-law
If you need to eat
So you went out?
I had to avoid my father-in-law.
the lock
Kaya said it was sweet.
To prevent anyone from coming in from outside
Ah…
Oh, that's ridiculous.
how…
no!
This is a conspiracy!
- What a killer bitch.
- Ouch!
How dare you snake-like bitch me!
Argh!
iced coffee!
Wow, what should I do?
Ha…
ah…
Oh, why don't you just pretend not to notice?
Lawyer
Something that can be quietly covered up
No, anyway
No matter what I do
It doesn't matter?
I just left there
I hope you can live quietly in Korea
I was hoping
Mr. Kaya
No matter how much you love your husband
Covering this up
I can't protect you.
Love?
I don't love that person
Lawyer
yes?
A person who met for just one hour and got married
Can you love?
ah…
I'm just my hometown
Because I hate it so much
I wanted to come to Korea
If you just let me get away from there
Anyone would have followed
I just
I thought I was doing my job
can you let me live here
Because they are people
But I
I ruined everything.
Even that person…
It would have been okay if I had left quietly.
me
I wish I could
Lawyer…
Mr. Kaya…
Application for change of cause of claim
I saw it
That's shocking.
yes
Fortunately, the blanket and underwear
DNA evidence was detected
The defendant's father was arrested.
This marriage is no longer
It's clear it can't last
Divorce decree as soon as possible
please take it down
Defendant
Do you have anything more to say?
Then, the argument for this case
I will conclude
The date of sentencing is...
Your honor
Hey, Woo Myung-hoon
What's going on?
As the defendant's representative in this case
Newly appointed
Power of attorney and counterclaim
I will submit it
- What?
- Uh
This case has already been closed...
Your honor
Please resume the argument.
no
Is there anything else you would like to do?
The reason for the divorce has already been revealed...
Divorce is
marital relationship
It has been validly established
Isn’t that a premise?
Now what does that mean?
Your honor
For the purpose of delaying the lawsuit now.
Making unreasonable claims...
Plaintiff Kaya
In my hometown before marriage
I have already had a child
Huh...
this…
What does this mean?
uh?
uh? Oh, no, right?
No
Plaintiff hid the fact of childbirth
deceive the defendant
It was a fraudulent marriage.
To prove this
Physical feelings about the plaintiff
Apply
I fell into a trap
A bitch with bad behavior
Stop being deceived...
Ah, yes
Yes, this incident is
Those kinds of things are needed.
Maybe
If you think of something to talk about
Please tell me anytime
One thing is certain
What is that?
I definitely saw it that night
Stretch marks on her stomach
I had stretch marks.
Stretch marks?
yes
Kay, Kaya, Kaya
Actually, isn't it?
shameless bitch
And the defendant
against the plaintiff
Marriage cancellation and alimony due to fraud
Counterclaim seeking 100 million won
I charge you
Filing a counterclaim
I will accept it
Will it be heard together with the main court?
I will decide later
Why didn't you tell me?
‘I have given birth before marriage’
Kaya, is that really true?
now completely
It's a new situation.
Annulment of marriage is different from divorce.
The marriage itself is completely invalidated.
I never got married in the first place
It will work
I came to Korea on a marriage visa.
It's all canceled
I'm getting kicked out of this country.
Lawyer Kang
I'm being kicked out of this country.
Mr. Kaya!
yes?
I will pronounce judgment.
no way…
This is ridiculous!
It was dismissed, Ms. Kaya’s appeal.
The father-in-law who sexually assaulted me is released.
The victim is deported...
Kaya's marriage visa was also canceled.
Expulsion!
Are you going to give up like this?
I have to find some way
- Let's go into exile.
-Where?
USA? france?
Wait a minute!
This is Kaya's lawyer.
We are applying for asylum
Oh, is it okay?
Of course we lose
No, of course you're going to lose?
Even if you lose the trial, you win the case.
To this clown
Are you going to make me a bridesmaid?
I may be a clown, but
This trial is not a farce
It's a fight
desperate